http://www.ccaurora.edu/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
ANNOUNCEMENT: Most spring 2021 classes will once again be offered online/remotely. Learn more about the spring 2021 semester.
Menu
About CCA
Community College of Aurora is a diverse, tight-knit community that offers quality education at two convenient locations and online. Students leave CCA prepared for the next stage of their lives, whether in the workforce or at a four-year institution.
Why CCA?
Campus Security & Safety
Our Locations
Our Mission
Assessment & College Data
Right to Know
Accreditation
Hispanic Serving Institution
Inclusive Excellence
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Getting Started
CCA is committed to student success and provides many resources, tools and support to aid students in their education. From enrollment to graduation, CCA is dedicated to helping students realize their potential both inside and outside of the classroom.
Apply Now!
Getting Started Checklist
Financial Aid
Orientation
Paying for College
Transfer to CCA
Assessment / Testing
Pathway Advising
Recruitment
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Students
CCA’s mission is to help students succeed in college and beyond. Cutting-edge technology, outstanding faculty, student clubs and countless services work together to ensure that students meet their goals.
Support Services
Mental Health & Counseling
Library
Student Life
Transfer Success
Military & Veterans
High School Students
International Students
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Programs & Classes
CCA offers over 40 areas of degrees and certificates to choose from, many as part of seamless transfer plans. Students can take classroom, online, hybrid and evening/weekend classes to fit their schedule.
Departments
Online Learning
Degrees & Certificates
Honors
Catalog & Class Schedule
Academic Calendar
ESL Programs
Guided Pathways: Academic Course Maps
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Our People
Each member of CCA’s skilled, knowledgeable and compassionate faculty and staff is committed to creating a comfortable and supportive learning environment for students. Students and alumni of diverse backgrounds have excelled at CCA and beyond.
Blog
President's Welcome
Faculty Profiles
Our Leadership
Awards & Honors
Alumni Success
LGBTQA+ Task Force
LatinX Faculty and Staff Association
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
News & Events
CCA is a vital and vibrant part of Aurora and a center for the community. The cultural and intellectual offerings are often open to the public, free of cost and occur year-round.
Event Calendar
News Releases
CCA in the News
CCA Campus Newsletter
CCA Videos
Photo Galleries
PR & Marketing Contacts
Quicklinks
Apply and Register
Catalog and Class Schedule
Job Opportunities and Resources
Refer a Concern or Incident
Transcripts
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Workforce & Professional Development
CCA proudly serves Aurora and the surrounding communities, engaging in economic and community development initiatives through workforce training, certificate and degree programs and community enrichment.
Workforce & Professional Development
Customized Corporate Training
Disaster Management Institute
Grants and Awards
Request a Room
Partnerships
Employer Connections
CCA Foundation
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Community College of Aurora
Home
»
Privacy Policy
Section Links
Apply and Register
Catalog and Class Schedule
Job Opportunities and Resources
Refer a Concern or Incident
Transcripts
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.ccaurora.edu. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to send you information.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new services or changes to this privacy policy.
Form Submissions If you wish to submit a form on this website, you may be required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting privacy@ccaurora.edu:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
CookiesWe use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site and to serve relevant ads across the Internet. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
This site uses Google Analytics, including Google Display Network Impression Reporting and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, to measure and record anonymous visitor data. This anonymous data may be used to serve advertisements via Google's advertising and Remarketing channels and third-party vendors to users on various websites. This site and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to this site. You can opt-out of these reports by using Google's Ads Settings or Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web.
Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
UpdatesOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately: privacy@ccaurora.edu
Locations
CentreTech Campus
16000 E. CentreTech Pkwy
Aurora, CO 80011
303-360-4700
Lowry Campus
710 Alton Way
Denver, CO 80230
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Connect
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
Blog
Instagram
Copyright © 2020 Community College of Aurora.
Footer
Home
Contact
Banner
Legal Notices
Privacy Policy
Search
Search
Favorites
Apply Now!
My CCA
COVID-19 Updates
Directory
Contact
Jobs
QuickLinks
Apply and Register
Catalog and Class Schedule
Job Opportunities and Resources
Refer a Concern or Incident
Transcripts
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Main Menu
About CCA
Community College of Aurora is a diverse, tight-knit community that offers quality education at two convenient locations and online. Students leave CCA prepared for the next stage of their lives, whether in the workforce or at a four-year institution.
Why CCA?
Campus Security & Safety
Our Locations
Our Mission
Assessment & College Data
Right to Know
Accreditation
Hispanic Serving Institution
Inclusive Excellence
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Getting Started
CCA is committed to student success and provides many resources, tools and support to aid students in their education. From enrollment to graduation, CCA is dedicated to helping students realize their potential both inside and outside of the classroom.
Apply Now!
Getting Started Checklist
Financial Aid
Orientation
Paying for College
Transfer to CCA
Assessment / Testing
Pathway Advising
Recruitment
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Students
CCA’s mission is to help students succeed in college and beyond. Cutting-edge technology, outstanding faculty, student clubs and countless services work together to ensure that students meet their goals.
Support Services
Mental Health & Counseling
Library
Student Life
Transfer Success
Military & Veterans
High School Students
International Students
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Programs & Classes
CCA offers over 40 areas of degrees and certificates to choose from, many as part of seamless transfer plans. Students can take classroom, online, hybrid and evening/weekend classes to fit their schedule.
Departments
Online Learning
Degrees & Certificates
Honors
Catalog & Class Schedule
Academic Calendar
ESL Programs
Guided Pathways: Academic Course Maps
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Our People
Each member of CCA’s skilled, knowledgeable and compassionate faculty and staff is committed to creating a comfortable and supportive learning environment for students. Students and alumni of diverse backgrounds have excelled at CCA and beyond.
Blog
President's Welcome
Faculty Profiles
Our Leadership
Awards & Honors
Alumni Success
LGBTQA+ Task Force
LatinX Faculty and Staff Association
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
News & Events
CCA is a vital and vibrant part of Aurora and a center for the community. The cultural and intellectual offerings are often open to the public, free of cost and occur year-round.
Event Calendar
News Releases
CCA in the News
CCA Campus Newsletter
CCA Videos
Photo Galleries
PR & Marketing Contacts
Quicklinks
Apply and Register
Catalog and Class Schedule
Job Opportunities and Resources
Refer a Concern or Incident
Transcripts
Third Party Refund Information
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
Workforce & Professional Development
CCA proudly serves Aurora and the surrounding communities, engaging in economic and community development initiatives through workforce training, certificate and degree programs and community enrichment.
Workforce & Professional Development
Customized Corporate Training
Disaster Management Institute
Grants and Awards
Request a Room
Partnerships
Employer Connections
CCA Foundation
What is Guided Pathways?
Events
‹
›
×
